antar.in 2015-03-15

# Privacy Policy

##  [ Privacy Policy](http://antar.in/privacy-policy)

Details
     Written by Srinivas Kuknoorpalli 

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Antar.in takes your privacy seriously.At Antar we are committed to safeguarding and preserving the privacy of our visitors.This Privacy Policy explains what happens to any personal data that you provide to us, or that we collect from you whilst you visit our site. We do update this Policy from time to time so please do review this Policy regularly.

**Information We Collect**

In running and maintaining our website we may collect the following data about you

  1. Information about your use of our site including details of your visits such as pages viewed and the resources that you access. Such information includes traffic data, location data and other communication data.
  2. Information provided voluntarily by you. For example, Information provided y you Such as name,email address etc on registration
  3. Information that you provide when you communicate with us by any means.

**Use of Cookies**   
We may gather information about your general internet use by using the cookie.  Where used, these cookies are downloaded to your computer and stored on the computer’s hard drive. Such information will not identify you personally. You can adjust the settings on your computer to decline any cookies if you wish.  This can easily be done by activating the reject cookies setting on your computer.Affliate networks & other third parties may use cookies or  scripts to track down visitors to our site in order to display advertisements and other information. Such tracking is done by the third parties through their own servers and is subject to their own privacy policies.

**Use of Your Information**

We use the information that we collect from you to provide our services to you

  1. To provide information to you that you request from us . 
  2. To inform you of any new changes to our website.I.e. about new features , site down for maintenance & etc

**Disclosing Your Information**

We will not disclose your personal information to any other party.

**Comments  policy:-**

We welcome comments from anyone on our site but we reserve the right to publish or remove any comments.

**Third Party Links**  
we include links to third parties on this website. Where we provide a link it does not mean that we endorse or approve that site’s policy towards visitor privacy. You should review their privacy policy before sending them any personal data.Most of the links on the site are monetized

**Contacting Us**

Please do not hesitate to contact us regarding any matter relating to this Privacy Policy at [](mailto:%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20var%20prefix%20=%20'ma'%20+%20'il'%20+%20'to';%20var%20path%20=%20'hr'%20+%20'ef'%20+%20'=';%20var%20addy24583%20=%20'admin'%20+%20'@';%20addy24583%20=%20addy24583%20+%20'antar'%20+%20'.'%20+%20'in';%20document.write\('%3Ca%20'%20+%20path%20+%20'\\''%20+%20prefix%20+%20':'%20+%20addy24583%20+%20'\\'%3E'\);%20document.write\(addy24583\);%20document.write\('%3C\\/a%3E'\);%20//--%3E\\n%20%3C/script%3E%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\('%3Cspan%20style=\\'display:%20none;\\'%3E'\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3EThis%20email%20address%20is%20being%20protected%20from%20spambots.%20You%20need%20JavaScript%20enabled%20to%20view%20it.%20%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\('%3C/'\);%20document.write\('span%3E'\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E)[admin@antar.in](mailto:admin@antar.in)
